negative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
mmm
hmm
Forbidden by the hand, the thief hates the thief, and Amitabha looks up to Amitabha.
Please join us with your master
Please cost
♡♡♡
Subscribe to our channel!
Mmm...
mmm
Mmm
Hm
mmm
mmmnegative verb ending used in informal speech (abbr. of negative verb ending "nu")
What is it? A fairy?
Walking what? Overdoor.
What? Fairy?
Walking What? Overdoor.
Good evening.
Let's hear it for Yuzuki's room!
It's Yuzuki's room again this week!
I am the manager of Yuzuki's room.
I'm Shunsuke Setoguchi, the mysterious beauty of the scrap heap.
Thank you very much.
And with Yuzuki Daikoku of Team Killer Whale
With Yuzuki Daikoku
This is this week's night looner. Please give my best regards.
Now, Mr. Okura, this is your 201st time.
And today we have one of our semi-regulars, Mr. Knightor.
I'm sure you'll be able to understand why I'm introducing you so easily today as a member of mc's side.
Yes, sir.
I don't know why.
Suddenly I'm in such a potty-mouthed mood.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
So we have one guest today?
One guest today.
One guest today, not two.
Then please introduce Mr. Daikoku.
Yes, I'm Serizama Ma-chan from the other side.
[Applause]
Yes, I am 17 years old, a senior in high school, Ukkara Serizawa Ma. Please give me your regards.
Please do.
You participated in the Mizuki Fest last year, but this is the first time for you to come to our room to deliver a message,
This is the first time for you to come to our room to deliver a message, right?
Uka, a few of you have already participated in the festival, and now you are finally participating in the festival.
It's finally here.
We are close to completion.
You asked us to support Uka-san and call her, and it's almost immediately.
Thank you very much.
Isn't it wonderful?
Serizawa-san, this is the first time for me to talk to you slowly, so I was really looking forward to it,
I was really looking forward to it, but you missed the first Yuzuki-no-ie festival last year, right?
I think my dressing room was on the way to the stage from Ukka's dressing room,
I was standing near the door and left it open.
I was standing near the door and Mr. Kawasaki probably noticed me, greeted me, and suddenly appeared beside me,
He suddenly appeared next to me and said, "I'm sorry about last year.
Did he really say that?
Mr. Serizawa is really small, isn't he?
So, I was in a very low position, and I was in a crouching position because I had passed by him once before.
Yes, that's right.
I'm sorry I couldn't make it last year.
I remember Mr. Serizawa's face with his slanting waist very well.
It's embarrassing.
I'm really, really embarrassed.
Then, that was my first impression.
I didn't expect such a big name to appear.
I was looking forward to that day.
I really feel like I'm apologizing.
It's outrageous. Please don't apologize.
I'm glad you are here today, and I ask for your cooperation.
Yes, please.
Then, Mr. Okura, please tell us what kind of raw aishin you are in Yuzuki.
We are broadcasting live on Satu's channel on YouTube on Mondays at 9:00 p.m. a week.
Setoguchi-san and Yuzuki Ogura of Sachu welcome guests every once in a while from the well-known scrapbooks of the last game of the via last game.
We will be talking about various topics with our guests.
In honor of the title of this program, we call the viewers "roommates".
We will be talking with Team Shashu fans, Tahmin fans, Naito fans, and Uka fans as well.
We will call you "roommates" only during this time.
If you would like to join us, please spread the word on Twitter with this URL and the hashtag above Yuzuki's haircut.
It's time to go now, so let's go to the first corner.
Let's go to the first corner.
Here we go!
This week's Uka!
[Applause]
Ugka's member, Mr. Serif Sawa, himself.
Uguka's week, as well as his personal week.
and personal week by Mr. Serifsawa himself.
Yes, that's right.
First of all, on May 17, we had an online
There was a signing session.
[Applause.
That's fine.
We're in the middle of a release period right now,
We're doing a lot of online signings,
On May 17, you signed a poster.
I signed a poster on May 17.
It's really nice.
Is it the one on the CD jacket?
It's Asha.Asha.
To my own personal asha,
I have a calendar for June on the bottom,
I'll leave it at that,
I had a big signing session.
I'm going to sign it.
I guess it's like a calendar hunt in the city.
In the city?
If you take pictures.
Yes, that's right.
It's a tiny one.
Can I have my picture taken?
It's the first one on the calendar.
You know what I mean!
[laughter]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I've been paying more and more attention,
Please stop the system.
I know what I'm doing.
That's what the poster said.
I know.
The online signing.
Yes, there was.
Isn't it wonderful?
I think there are a lot of online signings.
I'm sure you've done a lot of online signings,
Are you used to it?
I'm used to it.
I mean, there are about three of us doing it,
When should I go? There are still some things that I don't know when to go,
But they make me feel at home with their comments.
It's a lot of fun.
I see. That's nice.
Is there anything else?
And the day before yesterday, May 20.
I had a release event at LaLaGarden Cascabe
I had a release event at LaLaGarden Cascabe.
It was in Kasukabe.
[Applause].
It was my first time in Kasukabe,
I did an imitation of Crayon Shin-chan as the MC,
I don't know if you can understand it here,
I don't know what it was, but it was a member of the board of directors, Murahoshi.
I really don't know what it was,
I don't know what it was, but he was doing something funny.
I don't understand.
You don't give any specifics at all, do you?
Yes, they did. So, when you meet Director-chan, please do your best to imitate Crayon Shin-chan.
Please do your best to imitate Crayon Shin-chan.
I'd like you to ask him to do it.
Will she do it?
I think she will.
What do you think? Would you do it?
I think they won't like it.
But, in case you don't know, my specialty is mimicry, which is not similar to yours.
Is that so?
You mean you don't look like me?
Not even close? I don't know.
It's a very subtle kind of mimicry.
Some of them are similar, and some of them are not so similar.
So it was a variety of things.
It's interesting.
It's nice.
The next day, yesterday, we had a live performance at Sanrio Puroland.
That's right.
I did one too.
Yes, I did.
My favorite character is Pochakko,
I did a live performance with Pochacco and another character called Kogimun.
I had the chance to perform live with Pochacco and another character named Kogimun.
They were so precious to me. I collect their goods, but this was the first time I met them.
I collect goods, but this was the first time for me to meet him,
I felt a little bit like I was meeting him for the first time, and after the period of Corona.
I felt like I could touch him.
I see.
Because it was recently.
And then Mr. Pochacco was great, and he came to me.
It was like this.
Shushi, we were both like, "C'mon, let's do it!
I knew that, when you are precious, you become Mr. Pochacco, right?
Yes, that's right. I usually don't have a lot of "san-tsukkusan.
How about "Naito-san"?
Do you have a favorite Sanrio character?
I was raised by My Melo-chan when I was little.
I was raised by My Melody.
Oh?
I often say "My Melo".
I was given a lot of Scion goods.
Is that so?
Like bento boxes and stuff like that.
But I really want to go to Sanrio Puroland.
It's a place that night people can't go near.
It's too glittering.
It closes early.
Around 5 o'clock.
That's right.
I start thinking about leaving home around 5:00.
You like it without knowing how hot it is.
That's right.
That's why I want to go.So I'd like to go.
I recommend it.
There is popcorn.
There is also ice cream.
All food?
Are there any shows like this?
I haven't seen any shows yet.
Do you probably have a job?
Certainly.
There is a lot of good food.
That's nice. You have a lot of good food.
You like it, right, Mr. Komuro?
What do you like?
I like cinnamon rolls.
I like cinnamon.
I even thought about buying a ticket to visit Puroland every year.
You went there quite a lot.
I went quite a lot.
It's open from 10:00 to 5:00.
I couldn't go all the way around.
Really?
You can't go all the way around.
I take my time with each one.
I just can't stop looking at them.
I just stay in the merchandise area.
It's annoying to stay there.
I just stayed there.
I finished in about 2 hours the other day.
Really?
That's really fast.
What are you looking at?
I'm sure.
Where are you looking in Puroland?
Where am I looking?
The shows, for example.
I look at the merchandise one by one.
There are a lot of strong and cute ones.
I also wait in line for the meet and greet.
I take my time.
Slowly.
Why don't you go there? Just the three of us.
I'd like to take them with me.
Please do, by all means.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Let's start with waking up Ralph.
First.
Yes, that's right. First of all, I have to let him sleep early the day before.
I'll go without sleep.
All in.
I'm going to pull him along with Moa-chan.
I heard that they know they don't have enough time.
Those who go often can tell that they don't have enough time.
That's right.
There are many ways to get around.
How was the concert? How was the concert itself?
It had been about a year since we last performed live.
Last year, one of the members, Idori, couldn't make it because of the president's absence.
But it was the first time for the six of us to perform together.
I felt a bit nostalgic after a year,
I thought the Sanrio atmosphere made it cute and fun.
You were wearing something on your ears, weren't you?
That was Pochakko. I wear Pochacco.
Everyone wears something different?
Yes, they do. I let them wear their favorite character.
I see. That's nice.
Cute.
Lovely.
It's a good week.
Thank you.
It was like this.
My week is full.
Since it's your first time, why don't you have a personal week?
A personal week.
I know you're busy at work.
What's going on?
I went shopping. I did a lot of shopping.
A lot of shopping?
I did a lot of shopping.
I used to have a general idea of the price value of my clothes,
And now it has doubled.
That's a lot of money.
The price I want to buy one piece of clothing has doubled,
I think I have grown a lot in this one week.
What are you particular about? Fashion.
When it comes to fashion, I wear what I like,
But I don't want to waste money on something that is too expensive,
So, I don't know how to put it.
I can't say how much it costs,
I'm too embarrassed to tell you the approximate price,
But the other day, I was invited to an exhibition for the first time,
I was a little prepared for it.
But I was prepared for it,
I was not sure how much it would cost,
So I went there.
I bought some new clothes.
Isn't that nice?
Growing up
Hey.
Yes, ma'am.Yes, sir.
How do you go about acting?
I don't know.
I'm lost.
But...
I'm glad you invited me.
Is it by introduction only?
Oh, no.
What's up?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I was invited by a friend.
It's like an invitation to the office.
I see.
I've never been to one myself.
I wondered how I could go.
But there was Mire-chan, a senior member of Ebichu.
Mire-chan was there with her manager.
Maybe if I do my best
I wonder if you could come to the show with me too.
That would be nice.
I know you and Mr. Naito like to shop.
Have you done a lot of shopping lately?
Yes, I did.
What should I buy? Clothes?
I bought some clothes.
The other day...
Like a family sale.
I wasn't invited to that, either.
I was told it wasn't from my brother.
So we went shopping together.
He helped me buy clothes.
She loves it.
You're very fashionable, aren't you?
Because the last time you came to see me...
I made my own arrangement from vintage clothes.
I was able to wear it.
Because he's a fashion guy.
Fashionable man?
I know it's a bit tacky to say "fashion man", but...
But that's not a fashion man.
Definitely.
I like it.
I want to say it.
Fashionable man.
I'm a fashion man.
You shouldn't do that, Mr. Knightley.
You shouldn't do that, Mr. Knighto.
It's okay if you don't mind.
You've had a good week, both at work and in your private life.
It's been a good week.
It's been a great week.
Is that all for this week?
I'd like to make an announcement.
Today at 2:30 a.m. I'm going to appear on mbs radio "m-town" with Gri-chan, and I'd be happy if you could watch it.
I'm sure you'll be able to learn a lot of things about us, and I'm sure you'll be able to learn a lot of things about Grasshopper.
Dice talk, dice talk, dice talk.
I'll be fishing for the mascot of the Dice Dice Talk.
Really?
Tsurimama, get excited.
Mike's not on the mic.
Tsurima, you didn't show up at all.
What's going on?
The most exciting part of the show.
Can't you please show him?
70,000 times!
So, before the show, my roommates had asked me what I wanted the three of you to talk about.
We will roll the dice, and the person who rolls the dice will give the talk.
The person who is selected
The person who rolls the dice will get a cheki (photo) of the person who rolls the dice, so please look forward to it.
Okay, I'll take the dice.
Are they eating bridge?
Sleiman gives them to Arisco. Arisco, don't move.
She's not moving at all.
Sorry, I wanted to open it.
Thank you.
First New Year's special.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
He thought it was so cute!
I wanted to open a three-man show.
Zev said...
Please don't make eye contact with the person inside!
He's so cute!
He talks normally.
Someone could muffle his voice.
With a character of that type.
Don't talk directly to them.
I've never heard of any of them.
Don't make eye contact.
I don't like that.
Let's see what kind of eyes you have.
Can I see them at least once?
Oh, I want this.
Lately, I've been thinking that I'm a very idol-like person.
I see... Room name.
Yoo-Yoo, you gave me this as well.
Then, may I have Ms. Serizara wave it for you?
I think you can wave it here.
Yes, sir.
Let's go!
I wonder who it is.I don't know who that is.
Se-no!
Ehhhh...
I didn't shake this one.
Yeah, I was just putting it there.
Sorry.
It's okay to do the gauntlet.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
It's gone.
I couldn't believe it.
Okay, so the first example is...
Just like the one you just saw...
Where do you shake it?
Put on your cutest face.
Translation.
Hey, what the hell?
You're so cute!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
This is a show for everyone.
Don't let your guard down, camera guys.
I'm not talking about the three cute ones.
Don't you dare stroll in here like that.
Talk when I ask you to.
Good luck next time!
I'm sorry, I'm a bit of a nervous wreck.
So, Seri-sama...
You're the prettiest girl I've ever met.
Please stop laughing at my wild comments!
So, Ms. Serisama.
I've been told to make the face I think is the cutest.
Well, let's face the camera.
Is this just a face, really?
What the hell?
I'm listening to you.
Make your cutest face, please.
Cute!
It's nice.
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, my goodness.
I'm a little embarrassed.
A new member just came in.
She's really like this.
So, thanks to her.
I think she's helping me learn how to make a cute face.
She's under a lot of pressure.
Even though the cameras aren't rolling
I think it's new.
How long have you been an idol?
About nine years ago.
Since I was in the fourth grade.
Fourth grade.
Is that right?
That's right. For the past nine years.
You have a cute face.
I think you have to take pictures of all kinds of goods.
I have to photograph them in all kinds of situations.
Is there anything you're particular about?
I've been making this kind of face a lot lately.
Recently...
I used to do it unconsciously.
I've been getting compliments on my face from fans.
A face?
During a live performance
Cute!
So cute!
I've heard that I sometimes do this.
I did it unconsciously.
But I got too many compliments on it.
I'm like, "I'm going to do this.
I've become conscious of it.
Recently, if I make too much of a pouty face during a photo shoot
The manager warned me that I make this face a lot.
I think you use it too much. "Hips.
I said it over and over again.
It's nice.
Is there a particular angle you prefer? If you ask me, I'll say I prefer the right side.
I like the left side of the picture because of the contour, but I like the right side of the eyes.
I like the left side of the face, but I like the right side of the eyes, so if the picture is taken from the left, I try to go to the right side.
I think it's okay if you took a lot of photos or just uploaded them to your sns.
Thank you very much.
Let's go... with the dice.
Wait a minute!
I'm practicing all of a sudden.
I was practicing a lot earlier.
I'll give you a shot.
One shot.
Why did you start with the second shot?
That's what I was practicing for.
Okay, I'll take it.
Here we go.
Oh!
This is the gentleman.
Yes, his room name is Fumi Barley.
The most amazing person I've met recently.
for short
The most amazing
Awesome!
Awesome.
Losing spirit.Losing Spirit
That's great. That's great.
That's good. That's what I was looking for.
I'm sorry. I was a little angry with you at the time.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you very much.
So, here he is.
The most amazing person I've met recently.
Please.
Well... my friend...
Oh, I'm sorry.
He's so hot.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He didn't talk to me.
That's the athletic department.
It doesn't make sense for us to collaborate.
It's just gonna be so hot.
He's so cute.
I'm curious.
Listen to the first Mr. Naito.
Can I return the favor, Mr. Naito?
I'm still here.
We had the pleasure of bombing together yesterday.
I think it's Master Arin who let me bomb with him yesterday.
Even though I've met him in person.
I think he's amazing.
When she was doing my makeup yesterday.
And the makeup artist...
Momokuro-san just the other day, too.
I was told that Momokuro also had a 15th anniversary live performance just a few days ago.
On the day of the 15th anniversary concert
I've had a lot of staff members come to me for various projects.
Excuse me, I'd like to consult with Ayaka Denshoudan.
or "I need to talk to Nami about something...
Even though it was the day of the show, if I was free
If I'm free on the day of the show...
I'll get caught
Oh, you have to do this.
"Oh, this is what I want you to do...
I'll tell you what I'm going to do.
You know.
And after that
He also gave a long live performance.
I thought it was really amazing.
They did a one-man show as a group.
That's amazing, isn't it?
Mr. Akiki, you have thought a lot of things
I think it's great that you're thinking about so many things.
You are really cool!
Nice, nice, nice...
I thought so.
It's great that you're close to him again.
It is.
I don't know.
I want to talk.
Excuse me, can I ask you something?
That's great, isn't it?
Tell me about it.
Please tell me.
To put it simply, it's the opposite of what it sounds like.
In reverse?
On the contrary.
What's the opposite?
I didn't know.
What's the opposite of what?
It's a friend of mine.
A friend of mine
She was going abroad.
The day she was going abroad.
He had a flight to go abroad at night.
So he came to school before that.
And he was at school.
I told him that I was going abroad.
I thought he was going abroad.
You're not having fun, are you?
I said, "No, I'm not having fun.
And then my friend...
She sends me a line like, "Oh, no.
He said his ticket was yesterday.
He broke it.
I wondered if he was really okay.
I'm Yukari Bancho.
Yukari Bancho?
You're Yukari Bancho, right?
Of all the members here.
Yukkari Banchou.
YUKAKARI BANCHO
I forgot to drink protein.
Even though I worked out
It was so yukkari-bancho
It was soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Squats are tricky.
You forgot to take your protein.
I don't care about that.
Don't say weird things.
I'm sorry.
It's just that...
It's just that I'm so...
I can't call myself Yukkari-bancho anymore
I heard that story.
I'm impressed with her.I think she's amazing.
How did it go?
How did it end?
I had to get another ticket the next day.
She went abroad.
They're all in the same boat.
It's funny that you're not sticking around.
I want to go. Don't say that.
It's strange that you're not satisfied
I see. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
But I'm glad to hear you're talking about games.
Let's open the show.
Let's do it at the end.
I'll start here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no, no.
That's the worst.
Thank you.
I think you have the cutest face and room name.
Island Prefecture and Mr. Tomaji for short.
Ishikawa
Oh!
Let's do it!
You've grown up.
He's really crying.
No, no, no, I'm out. I can't help it.
So, for Shimamoto and Tomaji...
Semisera and Daikoku got chekis.
Oh, my gosh.
I hate it when they have the cutest faces.
I don't like it.
You're kidding?
Why not?
It's not my area of expertise.
You're saying?
Maybe there's a step you can take.
You do that a lot.
I'd love to see you in front of the camera again.
I'd love to see you in front of the camera.
I want to learn.
I want to study.
I'll watch it and then I'll say yes.
You want to study?
I'll understand when I study
I want to study
Won't you join us?
I want to study.
I don't want to
I'm the worst at this.
I wish you wouldn't do that.
I'd like to be invisible.
Okay, then.
Here we go.
He's so cute.
Applause.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
You've got your hands all in a row.
I have to have it.
It's not just an expression.
It's like, "Give me a cute expression.
Of course.
You're so cool and beautiful.
You tend to go for beautiful expressions.
I think they want you to have a cute face.
I think they want a cute face.
Do you feel shy?
Who among the members is the best at that?
That kind of expression.
Only Haru can do it.
No one else can do it?
Really?
What kind of image do you have of Shyisa and Daikoku?
What kind of image?
I get the impression that you're beautiful.
But you once complimented me on my face.
Yes, yes, yes, you're cute.
She said I was cute.
I often look at your instagram too.
Yusaki is cute!
Both are good.
You fixed it a little, didn't you?
Thank you very much.
I like how Naito-san feels when he's caught in the middle.
He broke his face.
It's the most embarrassing thing.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm so embarrassed.
I'm the most embarrassed.
That's fine.
Let's change the dice.
I'm sorry, but the dice are changing.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
The dice are changing.
Can I ask you to make your cutest face?
What?
I can't help it.
If it comes to it, I'll do it with you, too.If it comes to that, we'll do it together.
I recommend it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's easy to do.
If we do it together, we'll get in the way.
So let us share the work, we'll get in the way.
Then we'll do it like poof!
Okay.
Okay, I'll do it.
Let's do it.
Here we go.
So cute!
Cute.
Yes, please.
What do you think?
The voice was moving so much.
It's like it's all been discarded.
I got it.
Protein drink.
He's making a face when he drinks it all together.
Okay, last one.
Not this one.
Okay, Tsilima.
No, no, no, no, no.
What about the body, Tsilima?
The bottom one is Tsilima.
That's about right.
And don't use your scrubbing arm.
Use your index finger.
Let's start with the big tree.
Let's wrap it up.
Thank you very much.
END
Isn't this yellow?
Oh, no!
I'm making you cry!
Think of it all first!
Here I go!
Hooyah!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Here we go!
Room name, Shy Boy's Unrequited Love for Zafran!
What would you like to do for 200 times? The theme is "What can you do for 200 times?
200 times!
What can you do 200 times?
120 times!
What could you do 200 times?
One person didn't abbreviate at all!
200 times!
I'll talk in almost full make-up!
So, what could you do 200 times? I'll tell you what I can do for 200 times.
After all, what can I say?
Last week, we celebrated the 200th anniversary of Yuki's room.
It's not easy to continue something for 200 times.
It's not so easy to continue something for 200 times.
So, after all these years of accumulation
It was quite a big event for me.
It was a pretty big event for me.
Is there anything else that you can continue to do?
Please tell us.
Well, I don't know.
I'm not so sure, but when I like something, I'll do it.
You say that a lot, don't you?
Yes, I do.
I'm currently continuing with a personal gym, and there are idols that I've been following for a long time.
And I've been supporting some idols for a long time.
On the other hand, if it's something I enjoy doing
I think that if it's something I enjoy, I can continue doing it 200 times.
What do you think? How many months have you been going to the gym?
But surprisingly, since last October.
So you've been doing it for six months.
Yes, I've been doing it once a week.
But I'm starting to see some results.
Have you seen any changes?
I've heard some stories about that.
And I'm gaining knowledge.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And then there's something else...
I'd be most happy if my weight hasn't changed but my muscle mass has increased.
I've been eating a lot of different colors for a long time, so I'm slowly changing my mind about what I eat.
I feel like I'm getting healthier and healthier, so it's been a great experience for me.
And I'm still enjoying it.
That's great.
Yes, but right now, I love being an idol and working is the most enjoyable thing for me.
I want to keep doing that forever.
I'd like to go to more than just 200 shows, but I'd like to go to a lot of different places.
I'd like to go to 200 sites.
A year?
No, 200 a year is fine.
For work in the future?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'd like to go to that many sites.
Thank you very much.
Fast forward.
Mr. Inoki, let's go first.
Oh! I'm sorry!
It's all right.
This way!This way!
Do you have any recent brags from your googoo name Yukimosu?
For short
I don't do what you don't know.
You've been seen a lot, haven't you?
I've lost a lot of power.
So, Mr. Naito...
What are you proud of these days?
Recently?
Well, I'm sorry, but I've been talking about "recently" and I've been talking about Otakatsu...
No, I think it's fine.
As I mentioned earlier, I was able to go see Momokuro's 15th anniversary live performance.
And when I went to the backstage greeting, which was a kind of a benefit event, I met Tamae-san, who is a fashionista.
I told Tamae-san that I saw your new nails in Fashionista and he showed me a lot of them.
Oh, wait a minute... is he called "fashionista"?
No, they don't.
I'm not a fashionista.
LOL.
What?
You don't want to be called Miko?
Not even for real.
That's amazing.
And when I showed him mine, Arline asked me to show hers.
I was like, "Oh, that's so cute!
I thought it was so cute.
I think it's so cute, but at the same time it makes me look like a cosmetic freak.
It's so annoying.
Don't say it out loud... don't say it out loud.
And it's on the radio.
That's terrible!
Nai-san, you're fashionable. That means you all have the same image.
Coming all the way to the store...
As a fashionable man.
LOL.
Because he's a fashion man.
I'd like to call you a fashion man.
By the way, how are your nails today?
Today.
I haven't changed them recently.
I haven't changed them in a long time.
They're cute.
Fashionista.
It's a little hard to hold the chopsticks.
LOL.
Let me show you.
It's a little inconvenient that you can't close the buttons.
I see.
Do you do your nails?
High school students aren't allowed to have proper gel nails.
I chose simple nails today because they said that regular manicures are fine.
But when I saw some of the older members getting their nails done, I wanted to do it too.
Which one of your members is the fashionable man?
It's a little difficult to choose the fashionable man.
Who would it be? But Ayame is sensitive to nail polish and hair color, isn't she?
As for clothes, there are so many different styles.
I don't know.
It's a bit difficult to decide which one is the main one.
But Ayame is cool.
Friend-sensitive idea!
Well, I'll let you all have a preview of what's in store.
Yes, TOTEHANA
Ah!
Oh!
Oh! Yes?
Oh, well...
Let me ask you something.
What's been on your mind lately?
Oh.
What? Translation?
I'm so psyched.
Oh, I see.
Sucker pucker.
I see.
I see... what has made you swoon lately?
A crush?
Yes, I have.
You heard.
Well, it was just yesterday.
We had a live performance at Sanrio yesterday.
Yes.
And first, me, Ruri, and Riju...
Ruri and Rijiu were in with their respective make-up artists.
The other three joined us about an hour later.
And then Sora came to me.
She had a cup from that Sanrio collaboration that they sell at convenience stores.
There was a cup from that Sanrio collaboration.
It cost about 500 yen.
I would never buy one for myself.
Because it's 500 yen.
But when he brought it to me and said
And when he said, "I'll give it to you...
I did.
Well, that's very kind of him.
Well, I hadn't given her a present recently.
It was kind of sudden.
It's just sudden.
I got her that Sanrio cup.
And Ruri got a big tuxedo Sam.
What's the present?what a gift!
The collaboration.
I gave you a non-collaborative raffle ticket.
He gave it to me and Ruri.
How sweet!
That's a little bit sweet for a member, but it made me feel a little bit sorry for him.
That's so sweet.
That's a nice story.
Yes, it is.
But also... to Ruri...
The earrings you're wearing today...
She gave it to me when we went to Sanrio.
I didn't give her anything.
I didn't give her anything, but when she gave me these, I was a little bit touched.
What a gift!
But I'm sorry, I haven't given her anything yet.
You have to give them something.
That's right.
You're getting too quiet.
I don't know what they're going to give you.
If you go shopping or something, you should give it to him.
What should I do with it?
Maybe Moa-chan is the kind of girl you want to give gifts to.
What's the youngest in the group?
The youngest.
I see.
You're the youngest of the new members?
Yes, the first and second.
That's one of the reasons.
It's going to be a big sisterly gift.
I'm feeling a little pressure.
I'm feeling a little pressured to give her something.
I feel like I have to give her something.
Daikoku and Shash, you're the youngest, right, Sakamoto?
Yes, I do.
I don't get it at all.
There's no need to lie.
I'll go buy some juice from the vending machine.
I often send them back.
I'm a senior member of a club.
I see.
You want to be friendly.
I don't know how to put it.
I don't know what you mean by impertinent.
You don't know what I mean?
It's very dangerous. Are you okay?
But if I went with Ruri when I went to Kobayashi's...
She's a little younger than me, but she was there first, so she's my senior.
I sometimes pay 1000 yen more.
That's cool.
I think it's okay to pay 1,000 yen more.
What do you like? Food.
Yakiniku.
Which part of the meat do you like?
I like beef tongue.
Beef tongue is a bit expensive.
If it's all-you-can-eat, I go for ribs.
Young man.
Wait a minute!
I'm going to learn to talk in a room like that.
Young man.
I'm sure you're still good, Okuro.
I don't like fatty food anymore.
Can you afford it? Serizawa-san?
Yes, I can.
I couldn't eat it before, but I'm starting to like ribs.
I see.
You're often called the careless one.
Is there something wrong with that?
Well, I usually wear makeup.
You take off your makeup, don't you?
I was taking off my makeup.
Just the other day, I was taking off my makeup and found that I wasn't wearing any.
There are many times when I say, "I didn't put on any make-up when I was taking off my make-up.
I scrubbed my face with no makeup on.
If you think your makeup comes off easily today...
I wasn't wearing makeup today.
And then there's the innerwear that you wear under your costume.
We used to put our underwear in garbage bags.
Really?
For laundry.
That's true.
I was surprised to hear that they were garbage bags.
You must have thought I was lying.
They're cheap to put together, and there's a lot of people.
So I put them in those bags.
And while I was preparing my own...
When I was preparing my own food, the manager said...
He said, "Who put the inner in the garbage bag?
I thought, "It's the same as usual.
I was like, "I'm the one who's putting innerwear in a garbage bag.
It's like it's an everyday thing.
I'm the careless manager.
That's the position you've been in since your debut.
That's right.
But recently, the name "careless boss" has been attached to me.
The name "Inadvertent Banchou".
Until then, it wasn't so well known.
And when we started our radio show...
We had a vote among the members to see who would be the careless boss.
We had a vote among the members to see who would be the careless boss.We had a vote among the members.
And I got the most votes.
I was like, "Why me?
I didn't like it any more.
No longer.
I was like, "Why are you saying that?
I was like, "Why me?
I've already got a name.
I'm kind of the careless leader.
I'm the careless watchdog, so what's the big deal?
That's how it turned out.
You know, for example, when you're on a tour.
When you stay in a hotel room, you don't leave your key card behind, do you?
You leave your key card behind.
That's right.
I saw it in the title.
I'm sure you're right.
It's turning out to be a good case.
I just put it together.
I'm sorry.
I see... that's good.
It's good to have someone like that in the group.
It's good to have someone like that in the group, because it makes everyone feel relaxed.
You're smiling.
People won't get mad at you for that.
No, I'm not angry.
They laugh and feel relaxed.
That's right.
If you establish that kind of character, you'll be invincible.
Invincible!
But she's unconscious.
You don't do anything during live performances?
I fall down during live shows.
The other day, on the first day of the spring tour.
I fell down during a song.
It's a really nice song.
It's our future.
But I fell so hard and I was all alone.
I didn't know what to feel.
I was embarrassed during the show.
Embarrassed.
But that's the best part of the song, before the chorus.
I don't know how I looked when I was dancing.
I don't know what I looked like when I was dancing or what I looked like when I was singing.
I'm in that kind of emotional state now.
I couldn't find the position of the bamili.
You don't get confused about the position of the bamili, and you don't get distracted by the lights?
No, I don't.
I see.
Absolutely not.
You can't tell?
No, I can't.
Do you have any, Ogura-san?
Yes, I do.
I'm so scared!
Yes, please don't do that.
I see.
You don't have that?
No, I don't.
I see.
Ogura-san, that already means the same thing.
Yes.
Shall I slowly become a watchdog?
Don't worry.
It's a careless show.
Are you okay?
Mr. Saito, do you ever make mistakes during the show?
Inadvertently?
I don't mean mistakes... more like careless mistakes.
Oh...
The song started while I was blowing my nose.
Wow.
If you could have waited for me...
You just lost one of your own... from the stage.
I've got hay fever.
When we did the release outside.
I was outside doing a release, and it was already bouncing off my feet.
So I went to get my hair done.
So please listen to the next song.
What a mess...
What?
It didn't start with that hair
Intro jan jan jan
Oh, no.
I see.
That's interesting.
You must have heard a lot of stories.
Ms. Ogura, today...
I learned a lot about you.
I'd like to talk more slowly.
That's right.
I'll see you in a few hours.
Would you like to close this corner?
Yes, I do.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you very much.
So, as you can see...
Chie, it seems that you have a fixed time.
If you have any news...
If you have any news, please let me know.
Yes, ma'am.
We, Ukwa...
On June 21st.
Our first major single
Wonder Little Love will be released!
We are in the middle of a lot of releases.
We are currently holding a lot of releases.
The next one is coming up this Sunday, May 28th.
This Sunday, May 28th
We will have a release at Morishia Tsudanuma this Sunday, May 28th.
Please come and join us!
Please come!
That's it, isn't it?
You have a one-man show coming up, right?
Yes, we do.
September, October and January.
So please raise your hand and come and visit us.
We look forward to working with you.
Yes, please.
Ms. Ogura
Yes, Mr. Ogura.
Mr. Ogura, you're here. How do you like it?
I myself...
I've never had such a long talk with you before.
I've never had such a long talk with her.
I learned a lot about you.
It was a lot of fun.
We're going to spend a little more time together today.
That's right.
I'd like to get to know you better
I'd like to get to know you better.
so please come back again.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Since we're here...
I'm going to do the MC thing today.
Mr. Naito...
Ms. Seriza-san...
How was it?
I knew that you said...
I knew that you were called "Karibancho".
Episodes like this
I heard so many cute episodes
I was so happy to hear them.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
How was it?
I stretched it a lot.
You got me.
I got it, but...
I'd like you and the other members to come out again.
I'd like all of you to come.
Oh...
Can we come anywhere?
Not at all.
By all means, right away.
The six of us will be here soon.
Please give my regards to Mr. Kawachi.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Kouchi.
I hear he'll be doing a stacomi from 10:00 a.m. later.
I'll do my best.
If you're going over there, you can go over there.
I'm not here.
I won't say anything.
But you can say anything you want.
Oh, you know...
It says the showroom will be open tomorrow, too.
Is that true?
I see.
Okay. - Okay.
Hey.
Take an interest in our members.
Why isn't she interested in Mr. Kawachi?
It's embarrassing.
Come on.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me for interrupting.
Well then... let's say a final word to Mr. Lumen.
Let's say a few words to Mr. Lumen and say goodbye.
Yes, sir.
Today...
Well, I mean...
I mean, it was my first time.
Thank you very much.
If you're interested...
If you're interested, please come and visit us.
We have a lot of things to offer, so please come and visit us.
Thank you very much.
And now, Melik is இ.
Let's leave the mystery for the last time.
I didn't get a chance to ask you what "Byblon" was... in time.
I don't know if I heard it right or wrong.
I'm sure you heard it right.I think you're right on Byron.
I think it was written as a group or something bi-Bilon.
Because you commented on it.
I'm curious about the origin of that.
I'll ask you about that next time.
I don't know anything about that either.
Let's have him come back.
Yes, please.
And now, on to today's second guest.
Our second guest today!
This is Ms. Knight Orna.
You're probably wondering who I am.
Well, I'm here now, and I just got in.
I'm just now getting in.
I'm Night Orna.
Yes, please.
Pleased to meet you.
Honestly, don't you come on about once a month?
That's right.
That's nice of you.
Thank you for calling so soon.
I'm looking forward to welcoming you and doing my usual Yuzuki thing.
Well, Mr. Ofuro, please give us the title call.
Yes, this week's shaqi.
Yes, this is the corner where Shinbiya-san's member, Ofuro-san himself looks back on the past week.
How was your week?
We shot a music video.
Is this the first time you're talking about it here?
I've seen videos of me doing it, but this is the first time I'm saying it with my mouth.
But this is the first time I'm saying it out loud.
We shot a music video for a new song.
I'm looking forward to the release of the video.
Don't mention it again.
I can't say anymore.
It's a new song.
You mean you haven't even revealed the title?
I can't tell you anything.
When is it due?
June.
So it will be soon.
The week after next is June?
What's it like?
Bubbly and cheerful.
It's nice.
I think it shows what's good in Shaqi.
Is that what the content is about?
I think there have been a lot of cool music videos recently.
Like the Shaqiflee music video?
I think there have been a lot of cool music videos, like the one for Horizon.
I have a feeling that it's going to be a pretty music video.
Please look forward to it!
It's going to be great!
Did you do this in one day?
We did it in one day.
Please look forward to it.
We also did a lot of other things.
We had the Tokyo performance of the "Chartifre Live".
We did it in Nagoya, but we did it in Tokyo.
How was it?
Charch Freres is a group of people from Aichi prefecture.
It is a collaboration unit of Coming Flavor and Team Shaqchi, both of which are based in Aichi Prefecture.
We performed in Nagoya and Tokyo, and it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun and it was great to work with not only Shaqi but also other idols
It was a lot of fun to perform with idols who are not only Shachi but also different from STAPLA.
I think there were a lot of fans who had never met each other before.
I think there were a lot of fans who were new to us, but since we had a lot of Shaqiflee activities
We met a lot of new people.
In fact, some of our fans came to the free live concert.
It was a day when I realized that we were able to have a very nice collaboration.
I've seen some great feedback about the live performance, and it seemed to be very well received.
I'm very grateful for that.
It would be interesting if we could continue to do this.
If word of mouth spreads among the fans
If the word of mouth spreads...
We're very excited about doing this.
The more it spreads, the closer we'll be to making it happen.
Also, the song called "Kaijin", which is a collaboration with Shachihure, was only performed live.
We only performed it at the concert.
We started streaming it at midnight on the day of the concert.
You can still listen to it now.
Now that we have a new song like that
I'm thinking that we might be able to make a second album.
But I don't have a definite schedule yet.
Please tweet me on Twitter while you can!
I'd love to hear from you!
I want you to do it everywhere.
I want you to keep doing it.
Even if you couldn't make it to the show, please tweet about it!
Even if you couldn't make it to the concert
I want to go next time.
I'm sure we can make it happen.
Please give us your word of mouth!
And, oh, what should we do?
Oh, hmmm, I don't know what to do.
Oh, but I'll tell you later.
What?
You're going to play hard to get.
I'll tell you later.
You're going to tell me later? I'll tell you later?You're going to tell me later? That's it.
The other thing is, I'm working.
Yesterday, I went to a bakery called Bread Tiger.
There's a very famous bakery in Aichi Prefecture called Bread Bakery Tora-san.
There's a bakery called Bread Tiger
Bread Tiger-san is challenging the Guinness Book of Records.
They challenged the Guinness Book of Records to see how many curry buns they could make in 24 hours.
The challenge was to see how many curry buns they could make in 24 hours.
And we, the president of the company
We, the president, participated in the challenge.
That's great!
It's really, uh...
We were supposed to help sell the Guinness World Records
We were supposed to help sell the Guinness World Records-winning curry buns.
But we were already sold out in the morning, and the curry bread was...
That's amazing!
So you mean you had passed it?
I wasn't sure yet.
But at that point, we were sold out.
We'll be back with something else.
We helped with the kitchen car.
Some fans of Tahmin and other bread tigers came to see us.
Some fans of Tahmin and Bread Tigers also came to the event.
Tahmin had people standing in line from midnight onwards.
It was a very hot day.
It was a very hot day, but they stood in line for a long time.
I was so happy!
In fact, the bread tiger even made the Guinness Book of Records!
We were very happy that we were able to witness such a wonderful moment.
We were also very happy that the Bread Tiger was in Anjo City.
The Bread Tiger is located in Anjo City, and we were able to help them out.
When people think of Anjo, they think of Bread Tiger.
We are also a group that is active in Aichi Prefecture.
We are a group that is active in Aichi Prefecture, so there are a lot of good things about that part of the city, and we heard some very valuable stories.
We were able to hear some very valuable stories.
It made me want to do my best again.
It was a day that made me feel happy that we were able to be a part of such a wonderful place.
It's a good thing.
And it's delicious!
Is that so?
It was really delicious.
It was really good!
You sold them? Did you eat them?
I had it for lunch.
They were selling an advance version called "Moon Curry Bread".
The Moon Curry Bread is in the shape of the moon, and it's in the shape of the moon.
So when you eat it, it's hard to get the curry bread batter around your mouth.
It's hard to eat curry buns because the girls are wearing lipstick or something.
Most of them are round.
Half of it is cheese and half of it is natto (fermented soybeans).
It's so delicious!
It's so good!
Did you have a special effect?
I don't know.
I was drugged?
It's so delicious.
Is that true?
It's absolutely delicious.
Right? It's good.
I don't usually eat bread.
I'm more of a carb guy.
Rice.
Noodles.
Not so much bread.
I don't know... I haven't lived my whole life liking it.
You're a rock star, aren't you? I can't live with what I like.
I can't live without it.
When I had the curry bun, it was so good...
Can I have another one, Mr. President?
The same kind of squidz at your winery.
Empty it before everyone else does.
I got a look like you're running low on hand.
At the bakery.
One more time, the white dress was wrapped in an open paper bag.
I was giving off the vibe that I didn't have enough.
The wrapping was so bad!
It was that good!
Oh, my God.
Bread.
I ate it for the first time.
That's about the extent of my encounter.
That's how you do it.
I've never been impressed by bread.
I've never been so impressed with bread.
It was a wonderful experience.
I hope you'll go to the bakery, too.
It's really delicious!
Of course, I've been doing a lot of activities in my hometown, Aichi, Nagoya, Tokai area.
I've been doing a lot of activities in my hometown, Aichi, Nagoya and the Tokai area.
You're getting stronger and stronger, aren't you?
That's right.
It's very interesting.
I'm really happy.
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
We'll talk about the other one later?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, which way do you want to go next?So, which way shall we go next?
That's all for this week.
Let's wrap it up, shall we?
Let's finish that popular section.
Let's end this week with the most popular section.
Let's put that popular corner last.
We'll go to the popular section last.
I understand.
It's hard for him to say.
I'm sure he's embarrassed.
Okay, I'll go to the popular section last.
Let's go to the other popular corner.
This week's Stapler Bulletin.
This is the Stardust Planet, of which we are a part.
Stardust Planet, of which we are a part.
We're working locally.
×X Girl Squad and
and Iginari and Okusan-chan.
We'll be looking back on the week of the two groups
and information about their upcoming live performances.
Place-chan just finished her tour a couple of days ago.
And they just announced that they are going to have a very attractive live show!
She's going to do a very attractive live concert.
×X Music Day
The live performance that we will make with the 3 of us
The date has been set!
It's amazing!
I'm interested in this one too.
First of all, the date is August 11 in Fukuoka
ZEPP Fukuoka
Tokyo on Sunday, August 20
ZEPP Diver City
This is the first time that I have received requests for songs from the members of the group.
We have received requests for songs from our members
and we will make a setlist based on them.
And we'll be playing with a band.
It's like a live concert where we take requests from the audience
So maybe you'll be able to hear something you haven't heard recently.
that you haven't heard recently?
that you haven't heard recently.
If you make a request, you might be able to see it.
It's really a dream come true for the members of the
It's a dream come true for all of us!
Please send us your requests and we'll do our best to make them come true.
Please send us your requests
We hope you will join us and
I hope you will join us and get excited!
I hope you will join us!
It's still a year to go!
We have a lot of events and things to do
I hope you will join us!
I hope we can make it a great success together!
I look forward to working with you.
What would you like to request, Daikoku-san?
Well, it's difficult.
It's difficult.
Today.
Today?
A sparkling smile.
Oh, you always go out in style, don't you?
I love it.
I love this song.
If it were you...
If it were me
I'd be smiling so much.
If it were me?
Because you and Mr. Kiyama are getting along so well.
You and Mr. Kiyama have become good friends.
Yes, we are.
Together.
Let's go.
Why?
Daikoku just sat down.
Into your face.
Oops.
That's not the title of a song, is it?
Sneeze.
What? Is that a thing? Something strong.
Oh, sneeze.
I was just wondering if it's okay.
I don't know if it's okay.
I don't know, it's just so classic.
I want to hear it.
I definitely want to hear it.
That's why I did it.
I don't know if I want to hear it.
Don't say it's a classic.
I've been thinking about it.
I'm a little hesitant if I think it's too sticky.
After all, you'll want to hear the standard.
Next, I'd like to introduce you to Igirinari and his son.
This is what I wanted to talk about during the week.
The other day, we completed the national "Never Lose" tour!
I was able to participate in the first day of the tour!
After I went to Nagoya Park, I decided to go one more time.
I made a request to my manager on the spot.
I told him not to put in any work for me.
Was there some kind of event?
Did you do it on your day off?Did you do it on vacation?
What did I do?
I don't know.
I haven't posted anything, please.
Oh, I didn't.
You made sure to turn it off.
I went to see Seto Kita's concert.
It was a very nice concert, though,
It was from Kaze-chan, the leader of the group,
I received this from Kaze-chan, the leader of the group, and I would like to share it with you as soon as possible,
I would like to share it with you all as soon as possible.
Here we go.
Kizuki, Runa, Setoguchi-san,
Kizuki, Runa, Setoguchi, and all the roommates.
Good night.
This is Karin Tachibana from Iginari Tohoku-san.
This week's Iginari Tohoku-san,
The national tour that started in March,
The national tour that started in March.
The tour has ended.
The tour has come to an end.
Wow. I'm so sad.
This time we went around the country for 21 shows in 11 places,
It really went by so fast,
But the time I spent with you all,
I was so happy to spend time with all of you and to enjoy each prefecture to the fullest,
Every day was sparkling.
The concept of this tour was not to lose,
I think that I was able to become a competitive person.
During the tour, there were times when I had to miss some shows due to health problems.
I sometimes had to miss some gigs due to my health,
But even if I lost, don't let it end as a loss,
I realized that even though I lost, I had friends who wanted to win with me.
I realized that even if I lost, I had friends who were willing to win with me and not let it end in defeat,
I am sure that as long as everyone like that is around me,
I thought that as long as everyone is like that, Jialin and Tohoku-san will not be defeated,
Through the tour, I thought that as long as everyone is like that, Jialin and Tohoku-san will not be defeated.
And then the release of the 3rd album "The Tohoku-san",
and the title of the Daichi fan live at Pacifico Yokohama at the end of the year.
The title of the Oichi fan live was announced.
The title is "Dawn to the Legend of Iginari!
Over the tour, summer, fall, and winter,
The moment of the legend that we who became strong make,
We will be happy to welcome you all together.
The fan club selection process has already started, so please check it out,
Please check it out.
See you soon!
Bye bye!
Have we done it yet?
No, it's been great!
Was it great?
I really didn't know if I should buy a penlight.
Oh, you didn't.
LOL!
I couldn't!
It was really like that.
We were just about to be late.
It can't be helped, that's for sure.
It's important to get started.
The Shimo-Pla research students were the opening act.
I wanted to see that, too.
So I rushed to get in.
I was able to see the research students without any problems.
I also enjoyed the live performance of Tohoku Sanchan.
It was great!
It was really great!
The level is really high.
And they sing really well.
It was really something.
But when I see idols live.
I get really...
I watch them very seriously.
Japan can't help it.
I look at them seriously.
I'm always looking for something different from myself.
I see.
I have an occupational hazard.
I had a lot of fun and learned a lot.
It was a really fun and educational day.
What do you see? There's a difference that I can touch on now.
Differences.
Which is not good or bad.
But there was a difference.
The ability to wink is also a big difference.
What?
Is that so?
That's huge.
It's huge.
Did he wink at you?
That's right.
Pearl and the others...
Oh, wow.
She's so cute.
I knew it was important.
Because when she sings, she can only move her eyes.
You can't do that with your mouth.
Oh, you mean making facial expressions, since you are singing.
Yes, because I'm holding the microphone like this.
The only facial expression you can make while singing is with your eyes.
I see.Oh, I see.
So, if you can wink...
You can wink in many different ways, can't you?
Like when you're singing.
Yes, that's right.
I thought that was pretty big.
Wow, I thought your wink was beautiful.
You're so cute!
Was it really bad that you guys were writing?
Come on, come on, come on.
I don't care if they say "Here, here".
So I thought maybe I should learn to do it.
I've given up about the third time.
Until now?
Yeah, I've been frustrated.
That's fine too, isn't it?
But I have to admit that I was very moved by your idolism.
I've been very moved by that kind of idolatry.
Also, Karen's words are really good.
Karen's words are really good, and they go right to my heart.
And I felt that she is a really great leader.
It really cheered me up a lot.
There is a song called "Song of Undefeat".
It was so cool that I almost cried.
I want everyone to see it.
There's a year-end event, isn't there?
Yes, Pasirico Yokohama, December 28th, I think.
Is that right?
The title is "Opening to the Legend".
I feel like we're still in the middle of it, though.
The curtain has already opened.
So this is where it all starts.
I'm really looking forward to it.
If you can take time off, please do.
I'm just wondering if I can take some time off at the end of the year.
I'm sure you're all busy.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Is that all right?
Yes, sir.
Well, that's all for this week, then.
Huh?
Okay.
Before that...
Yes, sir.
Daikoku Sasu and Naito-san...
I've lost it.
I'll put it on.
Oh, no! The video's gone!
Let's see the video.
What kind of video do you have?
I think there's going to be a video of Yujiki's room on June 3.
Rumpin will appear on June 3 in Yujiki's room.
I've interviewed a certain person about it.
I did an interview with a certain person about it.
I see.
I'm sure you'll be able to take a look at it.
Please take a look.
Yay!
Shachifre Live in Shinjuku
It's over now!
Just finished!
I had to leave in the spring because of the end of the show...
How was today's live?
Was it just a burst of applause?
Yes, that's Shachifre.
We're both from Nagoya.
But we're here in Tokyo.
You sing in the Japanese capital?
We're pretty much at a standstill.
It's pretty merald.
Yuzuki's songwriting was fun too.
It's a song about going back to Nagoya, the capital of Japan, in Tokyo.
And it's in Shinjuku!
That's a lot!
I was born to a lot of people before I came here.
I was born to a lot of people and lived in the countryside.
I'm filled with emotion.
But, after all, if you tell the people of Shinjuku
First of all
First of all, you're so strong!
Get their permission.
I'll go to Shinjuku, then sing in Shibuya.
Shinagawa next.
Really? Shinagawa next.
What's Shinagawa?
Shinagawa?
Shinagawa. Minato Ward.
Shinagawa station is in Minato Ward.
Minato-ku girls? Around there?
And so on.
Fashionable people will understand.
I know nothing but words.
I don't know anything about cultural history.
I've never met...
Fashionable people.
Someone from the port district.
Maybe he's a cleaner.
Maybe.Probably.
So.
I don't know.
If you're a girl from Minato-ku...
I'd like you to write down the benefits.
That's me.
I'm from Nagoya.
Nagoya's local spirit is fun.
That's what I want to show.
I want to show that.
Let's have the Minato Ward Women's War Olympics.
Really?
We won't do it.
We won't.
You're just saying random things.
Seven.
And speaking of Shinjuku
There are times when we can talk about exchanging capitals one more time
There are times when we can talk about it, aren't there?
June 3rd.
You should be here.
Yuzuki's Hair Fest will be held in Shinjuku again!
Yay!
We are doing it again this time!
We will have two parts!
Team Shachi will be there!
Team Shachi will be performing at both parts of the festival!
Thank you very much.
Thank you for having us.
You're the first one.
I guess I'm a little late to the party.
Of all the guests.
I wasn't sure if I'd be able to do it.
Last year, you invited me.
I don't know about this year.
It was on the schedule.
But I wasn't asked to do anything beforehand.
That's right.
It was a little close.
Yeah, it was close.
It was pretty close.
A lot... probably other things, too.
Amefura and the others...
The orcas were still undecided.
But yeah...
It's possible.
It's not a given.
You know, the people on the show...
They're great people.
It's possible that the orca's slot was taken.
Maybe...
I was wondering...
Loomis Blow was there this time.
It was a close call.
That's right.
The number of people in the room was also close.
That's funny.
I thought we were on the same page.
Laughs.
Not at all.
It was so sudden.
He just said yes.
Laughing.
He said yes.
This time...
The three of them called me.
They told me again that they want to live an enjoyable life.
I want to say it.
And Sato was in the mood, so...
He was in the groove.
I don't mean "in the groove," I mean "in the groove.
I was in the groove.
Laughs.
I knew it.
I was in the groove, so I'm going to enjoy my life again.
You know, opening that curtain.
So many things.
We had so much fun, didn't we?
Mr. Tohoku, Lou Maybrough.
Amefura, Tohoku-san, and Shachi.
Basho...
You said Northeast twice.
Basho.
And you too, Lightbulb.
Thank you for saying that.
It was really great.
I didn't expect to see you at the Yujiki Hair Festival.
I'm so happy.
It's been going on for a long time.
You know...
So many of my favorite girls are appearing this time.
Yeah.
There are a lot of girls I like.
But I think it's going to be that way.
I don't know.
I mean...I don't know...
I'm becoming more and more of a Stapler nerd?
I don't know, maybe it's that.
Maybe it's that way.
On the contrary.
I'm spreading it around.
I'm basically a junior.
The junior staff at StarPlaza are really nice.
Yeah, they are.
They're all really nice.
And they inspire me.
I don't know...
I mean...
It's like...
It's like Bon Festival.
Oh...
Have fun with everyone.
Yeah, like that.
I'm so happy
I hope you guys feel the same way.
That it's like Obon.
It's not a new ceremony.
Oh, yeah.
My roommates...
Oh, yeah
I'm a member of Setoguchi Hatsukumiai, in case you're wondering.
I see...
Roommates too.
So it's Bon Festival then.
Yes...
So...
So we're roommates in the new ceremony too?
Yes, we are.
We're members of Setoguchi's first union.
What's that?
LOL!
That didn't happen?
Yes, sir.
Are you guys Team Killer Whale?
We're also Team Orca.
Shunsuke Setoguchi is the center.
It's a big idol group.
A big idol group.
So we're a big group now?
Yuzuki's in it?
Yes, Yuzuki's in it.
What's our center?
Well, Setoguchi's first group...
Shunsuke will be the center.
I didn't audition for that.
I did audition for it.
Yuzuki's room today.
You didn't, did you?
No, I didn't.
You already did in the "Life on Fire" section.
Dressed up as Mojimogi-kun.
We'd already decided who'd be in the group.
So you've been together for less than a year?
We've been doing it for a while, but we've only done it once.
Oh, I see.
The second time.
Then why don't you put it in your profile?
We've only been running once a year.
Team Killer Whale Slash Killer Whale Flea
Slash Setoguchi Hatsukumiai
I can't get in.
LOL.
It's pretty low on my priority list.
I can't join when I'm involved in orca-fre and orca activities.
So it's just once a year for me.
But if Shunsuke becomes a little more aware...
Center
Yes, yes, awareness of the center.
He needs to send out a message from there.
As the same center, you know?
Advice?
Can I ask for your advice?
What's your mindset as a center?
I don't mind if you're a little angry.
That's right.
Shunsuke only speaks loudly when the camera is rolling.
That's not good.
That's right, that's right.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
He's a serious guy.
You're right, Shunsuke, there's a big difference between when he's loud and when he's quiet.
Fans can't underestimate that.
They want to see it.
They'll know.
So please be aware that you're the center.
Yes, sir.
What do you mean?
What is it?
What's this?
Yuzuki's hair festival.Yuzuki's Hair Fest
Yuzuki's hair festival will be held on June 3
It will be held at ZEPP Shinjuku!
There will be two parts, so please look forward to it!
There are only a few tickets left!
We want to sell out!
That's great!
Come to Shinjuku!
Let's have fun!
Bye-bye. Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you!
That's a long time.
I can't believe you didn't want to have a long conversation with her.
You said you didn't like it, but you made it longer than usual.
You know... it was a guest session.
I was going to end it in about 3 minutes, but it ended up taking too long.
And your voice was too loud on this side of the camera.
That's right.
Thank you very much, Sakura-san gave it to me again today.
I'm so glad.
I know you gave me some advice...
But really, June 3rd is just around the corner!
I mean, what should I do?
I mean, what about you two?
We haven't rehearsed for "Lou Maiglow" yet.
How's it going?
We're working on the song assignments.
And we've chosen the songs we want to sing.
We've chosen the songs we'd like to sing.
Today we're working on formations.
We'll do what we can for rehearsal.
We'll learn the choreography for each song.
We're going to meet in June.
Wow, so you guys are talking to each other?
Yes, we are.
What's it like?
Everyone gives their opinion.
That's great.
You too, Nana.
She's very forthcoming.
Is that so?
What song do you want to play?
And if it's a rumpus song...
she'd say, "You should put in a song that's a little more upbeat.
They'd say, "How about this song?
Because we all like idols, we all have our own opinions.
Because we all love idols, we have a lot of detailed opinions.
What should we do with this part?
It's amazing.
We are a good group, aren't we?
Yes, it is.
That's so cool!
The teamwork is amazing.
It's like we're all one-sided from the fans' point of view.
I'm glad to hear that.
It's good fun.
I may have already had it, but remember, on the day?
Oh, and go to the costume meeting around here, too.
Oh!
Thank you very much.
So you have costumes.
I was wondering if you had any ideas for the costumes.
Yeah, yeah.
Please look forward to it.
I really want you to see it.
Mr. Rune Maigro will be performing in one part of the show.
We only have a few tickets left.
I see.
I heard so.
This is a once-a-year opportunity to see Setoguchi Hatsukumiai.
Can you stop saying "big idol group"?
Also, they have it set up that I didn't audition for the group.
It also says that you were auditioning.
There are a lot of things that have been set up on my own.
SetoguchiThere has been no progress at all with the first group.
Rehearsals.
There is no group line, right?
No, there is not.
Because I don't know anything about LINE.
I've only heard about it in the comments section of Instagram.
It's too public.
Only the names of the stories are mentioned.
It's a big disclosure.
One of them always closes the story with a "hello" message.
I think that's proof that there will be no next turn.
There will be no next turn.
Three, one, two, three.
Boo-boo...is that so?
I don't know, but the fact that they are saying "female student" means...oh yeah, that's right, they were talking about something that wasn't there last week.
I was talking about something like that last week when we did the 200th meeting.
But since you are the center, I want you to pull me there.
I can't reach anyone.
I'm not even connected to the manager.
How am I supposed to ask for help?
But it's important to have a good heart.
I've been thinking, "I'll do it.
You mean you'll be here on June 3rd?
I'm sure Popopo will help me figure it out.Maybe Poppo-chan can help me figure it out.
I'll do my best to find out.
If I see Setoguchi-san's motivation...
I'm sure he'll make a move.
You don't have to say that.
Then I won't.
Only you want to see it.
I think everyone wants to see you... thick Setoguchi.
I don't know what's going to happen.
Enjoy your life... and remember how to pretend.
I'm not going to teach you anymore
I'm counting on you.
I taught you once, a year ago.
I don't remember, it's a once a year activity.
Then watch the video and memorize it.
You can do it yourself.
Or your own original dance.
If you're okay with that, that's fine.
Original dance is totally fine.
If you pretend to be different in the center, they won't notice.
Is that so?
That's right.
That's true.
That's a good lesson for me.
If you shake it off...
With a look that says, "This is the right thing to do.
After the whole thing is wrong.
And then the whole thing goes wrong.
I'm not wrong.
You have to be pretty determined to get it right.
But you know, Seitoku Tsu's first union was part one and part two.
With Stapler's students.
We have two parts.
We have two parts to perform.
Dan-Nai-Nai-san, you know, the second part.
Without singing
What's the world like?
What do you mean?
MC?
As a member of the Seitoku Tsu Hatsukumiai
That's true, isn't it?
What are you going to do? Do a part of it.
Seitoku Tsu, take down the center and put up the Rumpum Center.
Isn't this great?
It's a bit forced.
He says it's weak.
Maybe that's part of the script.
That's in the script?
That's what it looks like.
Oh, God.
Then I'm not part of it anymore.
No, you're not.
You're a selfish member.
I'm gone.
Oh, and by the way...
Last time backstage.
It was my own private dressing room.
And all I saw was a bunch of scrappers.
I don't feel at home backstage.
Please, please, make a scrap dressing room.
Don't come into the other dressing rooms.
I don't mind.
Mr. Mizukami...
Mr. Mizukami, your fake dad... they're so big.
I peeked in.
There were three of them standing there.
Even though I was backstage.
I'm working on a regular scrap job.
He's working so hard.
He's saying, "It's a lot of work.
I'll take care of it.
Maybe we can make a scrap triangular shop.
Depends on what Mr. Setoguchi says.
I'll be sure to tell him you're up for it.
I'm counting on you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Already the week after next?
I'm really looking forward to it.
Oh, man.
I'm so excited.
This is the third year I'm looking forward to it.
And there are only a few days left.
I'm sure we'll be able to bring you as much of the Yusukinagaya worldview as possible
I'm sure we'll be able to show you as much of the world of Yusukinagaya as possible at the show.
Lumen, I'd love for you to come to our show.
Please come!
Is this actually the end of the week?
We're still good.
Yes, it is.
Yes, it was.
This week's night orna.
All right.
Thank you very much.
What kind of section is this?
This is the section that introduces a week in the life of Night Orna.
Thank you very much.
So, first of all, this week...
Yesterday, I performed as a back-up dancer for Ayaka Nation 2023.
Thank you very much!
I've already had a lot of lessons for Ayakane this week.
I've been performing several times every year.I've performed at the festival several times each year.
The number of songs and content of the Ayaka Nation has actually been increasing.
But at the same time, they have also increased the number of songs we perform.
This year, if you include the interludes, we've already performed almost 20 songs.
Among them, Harry Mallon and I have been performing a lot.
Kana-chan has been working on the concept of the show.
There are a lot of stuffed animals and dolls.
We back-up dancers were dressed as dolls.
We were dressed as stuffed bunnies.
The new song "KIRARIN" from the Arin show
The song was called "Kira Rin" and it had lyrics about a bunny jumping around.
I got to dance with him there.
I also got to ride on a trolley.
It was the first time in my life to ride on a trolley.
When I met Aryn Shaw
You must be very happy to see the trolley.
I'm so happy.
I can't believe I'm saying that to you.
He said I'm so happy.
I said, "I'm so happy.
I'm so happy to be able to go around in a roundabout way
I really jumped into the Arlin world this year
it's been a long time since I've heard a lot of Prynov's voice
Garage Japan
Everyone was saying how cute Arline is.
It was a day when I could already feel the passion of Ms. Plinov.
You're so full of life, aren't you?
You're so full of life!
Thank you very much.
It's a valuable experience.
I'm glad we're taking it one year at a time.
It's been fun.
Thank you very much.
Is there anything else?
The other thing is that every Friday, I do the Luncheon Time broadcast.
This week we had Korean food.
Oh, wow.
You're off again.
What did I tell you?
I didn't predict last week.
I didn't do it last week.
It's not what I expected.
Yes, it was.
I had a bit of a schedule on Friday.
So we're going to send it out on Thursday.
Maybe this week, maybe it's going to be like not Friday again, so
I'm doing it like it's Friday.
We'll do it again, so please check it out.
Thank you very much.
That's all.
Waffle
Waffle?
Waffle.
What type? It's like a sweet.
I don't know...
It's like a waffle with meat or something.
That way...
That's the one... Prosciutto.
That's right.
Let's go with the ham type.
That kind of waffle.
I mean, if you guessed, you'd be wrong.
I realized about two weeks ago.
I realized about two weeks ago that if I predicted this or that, I'd be wrong for sure.
It's rather difficult, isn't it?
Not at all.
But I've already made up my mind.
The next time I do this...
And the week after that...
So it's already decided.
So you can't change it.
Then there might be a possibility of waffles.
Yes, there might be.
That's for sure.
Daito-san laughed.
On the contrary, I like waffles.
I was thinking about it.
Then maybe there will be waffles in two weeks.
Maybe there will be waffles.
So you have a budget?
Yes, I do.
What's your budget now?
1,000 yen.
2,000 TikTok followers.
The week I said that, I get to eat 2,000 yen worth.
Oh, I see.
When it reaches 3,000, it's about 3,000 yen.
That's what it's going to be.
1,000 yen.
For someone who calls it 1,000 yen...
It's very stylish.
And the volume of food looks delicious.
Just until the last minute.
Pick and choose.
I'm looking for something like 990 yen.
I'm looking for something for 990 yen.
I think we're off by two weeks this time.
I think it'll be like Daikoku-san said, like rice, omelet and grilled fish.
I'm sure it will be a Japanese set meal like Daikoku-san said.
I'm looking forward to the next episode!
Please check it out!Please take a look!
Please do.
Is that all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
That's it for this week's Knight Luna.
And now, as we come to the end...
I'd like to make some announcements.
First of all, let's hear from Mr. Naito.
First of all, this Sunday
This Sunday, we'll be having a performance by the Namie Girls' First Union.
I'll be performing with you again!
The official selection process ends today at 11:59 p.m.
The official selection period ends at 11:59 p.m. today.
So if you're interested in going, please don't miss it!
If you are interested in going to the show, please come to
at Spotify O East in Shibuya.
We will have a two-part show at Spotify O East in Shibuya.
If you are interested in going, please let me know.
If you are interested in going, please come and see us!
I also update my TikTok everyday.
We are also on Instagram and Twitter.
Please follow us on Twitter and Instagram.
Thank you very much.
Is that all?
Okay, thank you very much.
Okay, let's go to Mr. Orca.
Yes, Orca was made by Kenta Matsuguma on June 28th.
Kenta Matsuguma wrote a song for us.
The song "Waiting Bear" will be released on June 28th!
I'm so excited!
Kenta Matsuguma wrote 4 songs for us!
We are currently on a free live tour with the EP.
We are also going on a free live tour with the EP.
This month on the 27th, we are going to Prime Tree Akaike
This is in Aichi prefecture.
The next day, 28th, we will be at Morinomiya Q's Mall
We'll also be in Osaka.
Yes, we will!
I'll also be in Nagoya, of course, and Tokyo, and so on.
I'm also going to visit Iwata Shizuoka.
If there is a place near you, please let me know.
There will be special benefit events and so on.
There will be different events for different parts of the show.
We hope you will enjoy the show as well!
We're looking forward to seeing you there!
And...
What's with this expression?
It looked like he was going to do it.
And on July 9th
Diner Shachi, a performance produced by Team Shachi
Diner Shachi will be held
One part of the show will be a birthday party for OGRUZEKI
The second part of the birthday party will be produced by the members.
We are steadily preparing for some of the birthdays.
It's been a long time since we had a one-man live concert at a live house where we can do our voices well.
It's been a long time since I've performed at a one-man live house where I can make a full vocal performance.
We hope that everyone will get really excited and join in the fun!
We have woven many legends in the past, such as drops of water falling from the top of the stage.
We have woven many legends in the past.
I hope we can make that legend again with everyone.
I hope you'll do your voice training on that day.
I hope you'll do your voice training, get fit and eat a lot of food.
I hope you will do your body training and eat a lot of food on that day.
We are looking forward to seeing you at both the birthday party and the Diner Shachi.
We are looking forward to seeing you all!
And of course, on July 22nd, we will be holding the Orca Festival at Nagoya Castle!
This is a big summer event that we have been doing every year since we started Team Shachioco.
Last year, after a long absence, the Killer Whale Festival finally came back!
Last year, we were able to make a very nice Shachi-Sama, but this time, we are able to make him sing out even more.
This time, he can even sing out his voice.
This time, we will be able to use our voice as well, and it will be at Nagoya Castle, where we were born.
I'm sure it will be a very passionate orca with a lot of feelings and emotions.
The setlist is gradually being prepared.
It's not really coherent in a good way.
It's not all in a neat frame.
I think it's just like Shachi, but not too clean.
I think you can see orcas that are not too clean, that are not too clean, that have not been done in a while.
I want to do this and do that.
Orcas are always saying what they want to do.
I hope to share this space with everyone and have fun!
We are looking forward to seeing you!
You said you reserved a T-shirt.
There was an announcement on the merchandise page.
Some really cute T-shirts!
It's been a while since we've released T-shirts as merchandise.
So I hope you will wear it and come to the show.
I'm sure it will be very hot, so I'm looking forward to seeing you there.
It's going to be very hot, and it's the end of July, so please take precautions against heat stroke.
So please take precautions against heat stroke and enjoy the show in good health!
There are a lot of other things going on as well.
Please check out our social networking sites.
Please check out our SNS!
That's all for now.
Thank you very much.
As I mentioned before, the pre-order for the official Chassis 2023 T-shirt
The order for the official T-shirt of Mr. Chassis 2023 is until 23:59 on Sunday, May 28th.
Please do so as soon as possible.
If you forget, it would be better to apply for it when you think of it.
I really think so!
We have black and white.We have white and black
We have big T's and dry T's.
Please look forward to it.
Is that all right?
Thank you very much.
Now, let's start with the scraps.
We'll have that announcement later, so please look forward to it.
Okay, Ms. Mizukami.
Okay.
Tell me... what is it today?
What is it today?
Today?
Yes, sir.
You're interested in the code, aren't you?
Today, we're going to play a real-life escape game called "Rescue from the New Kamen Rider Secret Society Shocker.
Escape.
I'm sorry.
Please don't just get the title wrong.
It's "Escape from the Secret Society Shocker.
Yay!
It's a collaboration with the new Kamen Rider movie, isn't it, Mr. Mizukami?
Mr. Mizukami!
What's the story?
In this event.
This event will be a completely original story focusing on Hachioji, a senior member of Shocker.
So even if you haven't seen the new Kamen Rider...
You can enjoy this event even if you haven't seen the new Kamen Rider.
What's the last part of the story?
What's that last part?
You can enjoy it.
That Real Escape Game... is going on a nationwide tour.
Will the tour start in Tokyo?
No, this time we'll be holding it for the first time at the new Minamihorie branch in Osaka.
When does it start?
From June 15th.
It's in Osaka.
We've just opened a new store.
It will open on June 15.
When is it coming to Tokyo?
In Tokyo, it will be held in Harajuku on June 22nd.
Will it be held in other areas as well?
Yes, we are still working on it, but we are planning to hold it nationwide as well.
Have you seen the new Kamen Rider, Mr. Mizukami?
I haven't seen the new masked rider yet.
It is still open to the public, so I will definitely go see it.
What kind of augmentation are you, Mr. Mizukami?
What kind of ogre are you?
What kind of Og are you, Mr. Mizukami?
What kind of Org?
I know what an ogre is.
Fish. Org.
Fish.
It's definitely not a fish!
It's definitely not a fish.
It's an animal that's been modified to look like an ogre or something like that.
For example, Kamen Rider Grasshopper Org.
Because it has a grasshopper face.
Even insects are called 8-org!
The fish augmentation comes out at the end of the movie.
I don't know...
I'm out of ideas.
After all the bugs.
And fish? It's too vague.
I mean, which fish?
I see... so here it is.
I'm sure the new Kamen Rider fans will enjoy it.
If you haven't seen the movie, you'll enjoy it too!
For more information, please search "New Kamen Rider Escape".
Please do.
There is one more thing, Mr. Mizukami.
The other one will be in the spring of 2023.
I see.
It's held every spring and fall since 2017, and 55,000 people have taken the V-type test.
I see... I see... I see... I see... I see... I see... I see... I see... I see...
As usual...
Why are you lying?
It's a web test, and it can only be done on a smartphone?
PCs, tablets and smartphones.
Yes, it's easy to take the test whenever you want.
The test is a unique exam that allows you to analyze your strengths and weaknesses, and you will receive a score report with your score.
The test is held from May 26th to May 829th, from Friday to Monday, May 1st.
The test can be taken 8 times from Friday to Monday, May 1, which is from May 26 to May 829.
Okay, I know some of you are not familiar with the mystery, but do you have any reference for me?
I'm going to show you a video that introduces useful information for those of you who are going to take the exam.
I see... the name of it is... a video guide to help you understand the riddle.
If you're interested, please take a look and join us.
Thank you very much!
How was your foot work today? I'll take care of it.
I'll take care of it. No, thank you very much.
And now, as I was saying, the Yuzukinokiya festival will be held on June 3rd at the Shinjuku Zep, and after the first and second parts are over...
After the first and second parts of the festival, the Setoguchi Shunsuke Birthday Festival will be held at the Tokyo Mystery Circus.
I told you in advance that it would be like this...
And we've decided to start the ticket application tomorrow!
It's going to start tomorrow!
Applause!
You can apply for tickets in advance.
Tickets will be drawn by lottery.
Yuzuki no Ie members
And Daikoku-sanAnd Mr. Daikoku.
Mr. Daikoku will be attending the event, even though he is on business.
We look forward to seeing you.
Yes, please.
The show starts at 10:00 p.m.
The show will end at 11:30 p.m.
The benefit will start at 11:30 p.m.
Applause.
This is what this is all about, isn't it?
Even if you didn't win the ticket
If you don't win the ticket, you can still participate in the event, right?
Yes, you can!
Right? You can buy the tickets with the Tokyo Mystery Circus goods
Tokyo Mystery Circus merchandise on the day of the scrapping.
If your receipt for that day is worth at least 3,000 yen
If you don't win a ticket, you can still participate.
I don't know what you are coming for, but at 11:30 p.m.
I don't know what you are coming for, but you can't see the important event at 23:30.
If you are interested in the event, please come and join us!
And we're going to have original goods as well.
There will be three of them.
I understand.
The first one is
Shunsuke Setouchi Birthday Celebration T-shirt
And a self-tucked sweater celebration sticker.
And, ladies and gentlemen, I don't think you'll believe it, but that's the merchandise!
Mr. Mizukami's mask is losing it!
I want it!
I want this!
Mizukami-san, you mean the real you?
Yes, sir.
What? That one?
I used my power at Yuzuki's house before.
We all did.
You put it all in there, right?
Mr. Ryuuninitou...
Ryuuninitou used his power to turn Daikoku and everyone in Kanra into Mr. Mizukami.
The power was a little too strong.
The masks are now available as merchandise!
We are going to sell these three items.
Does that mean I can only buy them during the Sweater Festival event?
I'll buy them now.
Where? At Tokyo Mystery Surgas?
He said he'll be around Tokyo Mystery Sargus.
So you'll be there a lot during the hair festival?
Wait a minute.
Why would you let us sell at Hair Fest?
There's too much going on.
So you can go somewhere and buy them.
If I eat the power, does that mean everyone can buy it during the show?
There's a chance at the second part.
Or even the first part.
You'd better buy them as soon as possible.
I don't know how many masks we can make.
This time, one part is done by hand.
I heard it's all done by hand.
Buy them as soon as possible.
The stickers are great.
What a sticker!
It has Setoguchi's face on it.
The glasses glow at night.
I don't need it.
Should I put it on the guy on the bike?
All the junior high school kids should put them on their bikes.
Really?
It's just that the real light part of the glasses...
It's manual labor.
I'm going to have to do it by hand again?
Do I still have to learn how to dance to Setoguchi's first group?
Or record my own karaoke?
It's the opposite of that.
What are you going to do with the stickers?
I don't think that's been decided at all.
Are you going to sing something?
I hope they sing something.
No center.
There might be something.
The details are still undecided.
Ticket registration will start tomorrow.
There are two types of seats
Two types of seats
And the price of the standing room is higher than the reserved seat.
Don't be fooled by this horrible system!
Please don't be fooled by this system.
Please think carefully before you buy!
We don't care about the last train.
We just hope you'll consider it and come to our event.
We're not thinking about the last train.
We really don't think about the last train.
We don't have one either, because we start at 11:30 p.m.
I wonder what we're going to do.
Please write down "Pew" for us too.
The last train?
I'll take the last train.
I've been the star all day.
I don't want to see you in the bathtub like that.
It's normal.
Next time, run.
Last train!Last train!
Last train!
That town
That town.
Come on, let's go for a run.
That's cool.
Thank you very much!
We have a few more tickets for Yuzuki's FES.
Please buy them!
Now then, Mr. Bath!
We had two guests today, Mr. Serizan More and Mr. Knight.
It was gorgeous, wasn't it?
It was gorgeous!
It was a guest that transcended the boundaries of the group.
Thank you very much.
Well...
There were over 1,000 viewers.
I was very, very happy.
I was so happy.
And Rumpin is one of the regulars, so...
Thank you very much.
I feel relieved.
It's a little strange to have Rumpan as a guest.
What should I do?
What should I call him?
I don't call him "guest" because he's one of the regulars.
I don't know, Room Edge...
I mean, "Let's get busy.
Room.
It's Room.
If Rumpin's okay with it.
Yuji and Yuji Fujiko have a certain worldview, don't they?
We'll share a room.
It's gorgeous!
Of course, it's stylish.
Of course it's stylish.
We have a corner every week.
It's nice to have someone who's here every week.
That's for sure.
Someone who's there every week?
I was thinking of Bakabon.
You call him "Uncle Lele".
I'll call him Lulu's Luna.
No, no, no.
Lulu's Luna every week.
What do you think?
Lulu's Luna.
Cool and stylish man.
Not at all.
How do you like Lulu's Luna?
Very heavy katakana
Very katakana
Only 3
Okay, I got it.
It's like Lulu's Luna-san.
It's the hardest thing to say.
From now on, when Roomba comes
I'll say "guest".
Lulu no Luna-san.
Lulu no Luna-san is coming!
High functionality
I'm doing it, I'm doing it
That's Uncle Lele Lele.
How do you know that one, Daikoku-san?
The regular one.
It's great.
Can I have the drawing too?
I'd like to go a third time.
Last week.
Yusuki's
The number one ranking of the member's name
Please guess the number one ranking.
It was the episode "I'm going to fall asleep, aren't I?
Congratulations!
It's hard for auntie
Maruichi Cheki with Yusuki's pattern
This time, a two-shot cheki
in commemoration of the 200th anniversary.
it's funny here
If you want Hina-san
this one is better.
We'll give it to you.
Please wait.
please.
Shall we go? We have a little bit of time.
Let me introduce you a thumbnail.
We received this from a room name super body system eco. Here it is!
So cute!
And, I used to play a game called "Roam Bar",
I was playing a game called "Roam Bar," where you can chat with people.
In the chat there, Eko asked me for a haircut for her thumbnail,
Oh, I see.
Yes, that's right!
So you were interacting with them. So you adopted me.
I was very happy to hear that.
Thank you.
Cute.
The 100th anniversary thumbnail.
It's kind of warm.It's kind of warm.
Next, we received this from a room name drill teacher. This way!
Boom!
Amazing!
That's exactly why it's so cute. The thumbnails are lined up back to back.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
It's amazing.
I can climb the thumbnails to see how many different guests came.
Thank you very much.
Everyone has good taste.
Next, we received this from Room Name Ass. This way!
DODON!
Oh!
How good!
I love the hand-drawn touch.
It's cute. Is it 200 with the clay child?
It's wonderful.
Very good.
Cute.
This one is also lovely. There's something dusty about Yuzuki's hair, too.
Thank you, Asu-san.
Thank you very much.
Asu-san, there are so many different patterns.
Next, Hino-chan is here.
Ta-da!
Wow!
Ms. Sutankochi is wearing Yuzuki's birthday dress.
Indeed.
And she's holding a cake.
You already know Hina-chan's illustration, don't you?
I can tell.
I don't even have to write "Hina-chan" to recognize her.
I'm so happy for you.
Thank you very much.
Cute.
The illustration is really good.
Last!
We received this from Husuhiron and Oh my baby.
Here it is!
Ta-da!
Oh!
Funny face.
It's like the heart of a person becomes one.
You guys are so good at this.
You put in all the information.
It's so easy to understand.
Easy to understand. It's solid.
I can tell when I see the bread.
It's like a thumbnail.
I wondered what he did.
Nice expression.
What kind of expression is this?
Everyone was wondering where Yuzuki's photo was taken.
I don't know.
What's so funny?
What an expression.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad that you stopped and made the good parts of the video like this.
You are all very good at what you do.
There are many things we haven't been able to introduce yet, and we have given you the subjects for them.
Of course, there is a possibility that they will be introduced again at a moment's notice.
Thank you very much.
Thank you all for the wonderful thumbnails.
Please continue to do so.
Thank you very much.
So, how was it, Mr. Naito?
Yes, it was great.
I was invited to Yuzuki's room again,
Today was my first time as a host.
The host side.
I don't often get to be on the host side myself,
So I was very happy,
I had not talked with Moa-chan for a long time,
I have not talked with Moa much, but after talking with her today, I found her very easy to talk with,
I had not talked to Moa much, but after talking with her today, I thought she was very easy to talk to and I thought she was very cute,
And I'm really looking forward to seeing Lumigro, which is now on line,
I'm really looking forward to it,
I'm really looking forward to the songs we're going to play, as well as the costumes.
I'm really looking forward to it, and I hope many of you will come to see it. I hope you will come to Yuzuki's club and Yuzuki's room festival.
Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Please close today with the two of you.
Yes, I'm looking forward to seeing you again around the time of Lou.
Please look forward to seeing us again around the time of Lou.
How do we close?
What's today?
What would you like?
Okay, bye-bye.
We're in the middle of a show.
It's been two hours.
It's ready.
Okay, bye.
See you next week.
All right, bye-bye!Seino bye-bye!
I'm so surprised.
I need a patent for this kind of thing.
See you next week!
Thank you very much.
Mmm.
Mm-hmm.
Mnh-mnh.
mmm